[
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Trade Payable",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Income Taxes Payable",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Dividend Payable",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Unearned Subscription Revenue",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Unearned Gift Card Revenue",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "event",
    "question": "Menghilangkan data keuangan perusahaan yang berakibat kerugian bagi perusahaan.",
    "reward": {
      "steps": -18,
      "stun": 1
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "event",
    "question": "Mendapatkan bonus atas keberhasilan menyelesaikan proyek keuangan perusahaan, dipromosikan sebagai senior associate 2.",
    "reward": {
      "steps": 5,
      "stun": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Communication Expense",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 3,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -2,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Decrease of Income Tax Expense",
    "correctAnswer": "credit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 2,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": 0,
        "stun": 1
      }
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "question",
    "question": "Increase of Interest Revenue",
    "correctAnswer": "debit",
    "reward": {
      "correct": {
        "steps": 1,
        "stun": 0
      },
      "wrong": {
        "steps": -1,
        "stun": 0
      }
    }
  }
]
